<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>!A improved backdrops</name>
    <directory>!!! improved backdrops</directory>
    <id>2751333905</id>
    <description>-- PLEASE READ! --

Make sure to restart the game when first installing or after enabling / disabling, otherwise the mod will not work properly!


The mod will not work with most other mods that change backdrops!
Works with and without StageAPI.

You can use Mod Config Menu to toggle certain features!
(If you use other mods that have custom rocks, make sure to disable this mod's custom ones with it!)

Best used with:
Nioffe's Better Doors (it has unique sprites for this mod!) or my custom doors
Darker Hell
Mega Satan's Bling
my custom devil and angel statues


----------------------------


-- Additions --
- most main path levels have unique boss (and mini boss) rooms
- some floors can have unique detail sprites (similar to the hanging chains in Gehenna or lanterns in the Mines)
- new Cathedral
- new Mausoleum based on the cut mini-floor from Antibirth
- new Catacombs
- new Burning Basement
- more variants for Caves, Necropolis, Gehenna, Womb, Sheol, Libraries
- new Angel and Devil rooms
- new Arcades
- new Challenge rooms
- new alternate path entrances
- new Black Markets

-- Changes --
- improved backdrop sprites for: Basement, Cellar, Mines, Depths, Dank Depths, Scarred Womb, Blue Womb, Dark Room, Shops, Dice rooms, Isaac's / Barren rooms, Secret rooms, Planetariums, Curse Rooms
- improved lighting and overlay effects for Downpour, Flooded Caves, Mines, Ashpit, Depths, Dank Depths, Gehenna, Womb, Blue Womb, Dark Room
- more fitting props / rocks / pits / spikes for a lot of floors


----------------------------


Also available on GitHub
I can be reached on Discord, PixelPlz#8363 or you can add me directly on Steam.

Thank you to:
Aleku for the better Basement backdrop
Nioffe for letting me use some assets from their Backgrounds and Doors mod
TheSavageHybrid for the base for the new Burning Basement
BeGrapa for letting me include fixed pits v2
Everyone else, for all the support :)</description>
    <version>2.2</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Floors"/>
    <tag id="Hazards"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
    <tag id="Shaders"/>
</metadata>
